{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "Question": "What is the difference between a Smart Meter and a Standard Power Meter?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Standard Power Meters collect data like a Smart Meter does, but need to be checked manually instead of automatically.",
        "Standard Power Meters are stronger and can handle more energy than Smart Meters.",
        "Smart Meters follow the metric system while Standard Power Meters follow the Imperial system."
      ],
      "Correct": 0
    },
    {
      "Question": "What do Power Meters do?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Power Meters measure the amount of strength between different electrical currents.",
        "Power Meters read the amount of electrical power used by a home, business, or device.",
        "A Power Meter is the part of a user interface that describes how much health your character has."
      ],
      "Correct": 1
    },
    {
      "Question": "How often do Smart Meters send data to the power company about power usage?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Never",
        "At night while the family is sleeping",
        "When the TV volume is changed",
        "All the time."
      ],
      "Correct": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the difference between the Smart Grid and Smart Meters? \n",
      "Answers": [
        "The Smart Grid applies to cities while Smart Meters apply to small towns.",
        "The Smart Grid refers to the network as a whole, while Smart Meters are components that are a part of the Smart Grid",
        "The Smart Grid is book smart while Smart Meters are street smart.",
        "The Smart Grid and Smart Meters are interchangeable terms that mean the same thing."
      ],
      "Correct": 1
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is NOT a renewable energy used for Smart Grid. \n",
      "Answers": [
        "Wind",
        "Solar",
        "Coal",
        "Water"
      ],
      "Correct": 2
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is a part of the Smart Grid?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Smart Meters",
        "Consumers",
        "Power Companies",
        "All of the above are a part of the Smart Grid",
        "None of the above are a part of the Smart Grid"
      ],
      "Correct": 3
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Smart Grid and Smart Meters are at risk of being hacked, since they are connected to a server.\n",
      "Answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "Correct": 0
    },
    {
      "Question": "Smart Meters can tell if an area is suddenly not using electricity, and will quickly resolve issues like this automatically.\n",
      "Answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "Correct": 0
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is Electrical Generation?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "A group of people born when electricity was first created",
        "The process of creating raw energy before it is sent out to people or stored",
        "The process of adding electricity to a generator",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "Correct": 1
    },
    {
      "Question": "Does the Smart Grid allow for upgrading over time?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Yes, the Smart Grid can be altered and changed over time as needed.",
        "No, the Smart Grid has to stay as it is.",
        "The Smart Grid will never give you up, never let you downâ€¦",
        "Sometimes, the Smart Grid can be altered but not by a lot."
      ],
      "Correct": 0
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is there a large amount of electrical waste in the Smart Grid?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Yes, the Smart Grid is very inefficient.",
        "Sometimes, the Smart Grid can be efficient... sometimes.",
        "No, the Smart Grid is very efficient and there is little waste."
      ],
      "Correct": 2
    },
    {
      "Question": "Is the cost for Smart Grid worth it in the long run?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "No, the Smart Grid is too expensive overall and not worth it.",
        "Yes, the Smart Grid is expensive at first, but cheaper in the long run.",
        "No, the Smart Grid will never be worth the expense.",
        "There is no Smart Grid, you have been fooled."
      ],
      "Correct": 1
    },
    {
      "Question": "How good is the Smart Grid for the environment?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "The Smart Grid lowers total use of energy reducing the amount created.",
        "The Smart Grid helps manage energy more efficiently so there is less waste.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      "Correct": 2
    },
    {
      "Question": "Can the Smart Grid tell when some place has lost power?\n",
      "Answers": [
        "Sometimes, the Smart Grid occasionally checks with the Smart Meters.",
        "No, the Smart Grid never checks the Smart Meters if the power is out.",
        "Yes, the Smart Grid always talks to the Smart Meters and can reroute power if needed.",
        "The Smart Grid and the Smart Meters do nothing."
      ],
      "Correct": 2
    }
  ]
}